<Tasks>
  <GetItem>
    <ItemId Value="2921338395"/>
    <!-- Can be found in the URL of your workshop item -->
  </GetItem>
  <UpdateItem>
    <ModuleFolder Value="E:\Documents\Projects\RTSCamera\source\package\RTSCamera"/>
    <!-- A direct path of your module -->
    <ItemDescription Value="A reupload of the RTS Camera, aimed at keeping the mod running for newer versions of Bannerlord.
This version will be updated for the current Beta version (1.1.0.10976).
Issues with this version could go to github Norbivar/RTSCamera/issues but I ain't making promises. :)

Save often and take care.

If you are upgrading from older versions and having problems:
- be sure to download/install both modules (RTSCamera and the Command system), dunno' why though, some people mentioned it was more stable that way
- try deleting all your RTSCam related config files (Documents\Mount and Blade II Bannerlord\Configs\RTSCamera)

OLD Desc:

Free camera mode allows you to give orders in the sky, as if you are playing Total War series.
You can control a teammate to continue fight and issue orders if you are down in battle.
Fix the bug that companions are always assigned to infantry formation introduced in e1.9.0.

Save compatibility:
This mod won't read/write anything from/into your save, so you can feel free to enable or uninstall this mod at any time.

Usage:
Press F10 to toggle free camera mode. The camera movement range is determined by scouting and tactics skill level.
Press E to lock to a unit when the camera is not locking to one.
Press E to control the unit that the camera is locking to.

Press L to open config menu during battles.
Check the 'Control Ally After Death' option to automatically control your teammate after you are down, to avoid your troops automatically charging or following AI's order.

Hotkeys:
F10 - Toggle free camera mode
E - Let the camera lock to a unit, or control the unit that the camera is locking to.
L - Open the config menu.
[ - Pause/Unpause the battle.
] - Toggle HUD.
; - Select character mode. In this mode you can select a unit by clicking on it, then press E to lock the camera on it. Press E again to control it.
' - Toggle slow motion mode.
All the hotkeys can be changed in config menu.

Credits where credit due: the original author and creator of RTSCamera: Izh

links：
Nexusmods: https://www.nexusmods.com/mountandblade2bannerlord/mods/355
mountandblade.com.cn: https://bbs.mountblade.com.cn/thread-2061243-1-1.html"/>
    <ChangeNotes Value="- character should no longer auto-charge upon leaving control" />
    <!-- Insert patch notes -->
    <Tags>
      <!-- You can use the following tags: -->
      <!-- Type: Graphical Enhancement, Map Pack, Partial Conversion, Sound, Total Conversion, Troops, UI, Utility, Weapons and Armour -->
      <!-- Setting: Native, Antiquity, Dark Ages, Medieval, Musket Era, Modern, Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Oriental, Apocalypse, Other -->
      <!-- Game Mode: Singleplayer, Multiplayer -->
      <!-- Compatible Version: e1.9.0, v1.0.0,... The currently available versions can be found at the Steam Workshop "Browse by Tag" section -->
      <Tag Value="UI"/>
      <Tag Value="AI"/>
      <Tag Value="Singleplayer"/>
      <Tag Value="v1.1.0" />
    </Tags>
  </UpdateItem>
</Tasks>